Justin Weicht

Mississauga, ON L5N1B5 justinweicht11@gmail.com 2899376338

I am extremely motivated for an opportunity to work in the HVAC/R field full-time. I will work hard to not only maintain, but exceed the expectations of customers and employer.

I currently posses my G2, ODP, 363 IPEX, Gastite, WHMIS, Working at Heights and G drivers license along with a clean driving record. My experience includes 5 years of construction (mostly consists of installing fences, decking and weeping tile systems) and 3 years of fixing and maintaining furnaces. I am also more than willing to obtain any other licenses that are within my right to acquire upon request.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Appliance Installer

Appliance Squad Ltd - Vaughan, ON January 2019 to Present

Installation of high-end appliances where attention to detail, time management, and work efficiency are skills that are demanded daily.

Heating Technician

Self-employed - Etobicoke, ON December 2015 to Present

I have helped a family member maintain his rental units. Whenever the tenant had a problem with their heating, I have always completed the job in a timely, diligent and successful manner.

Usually the calls involved replacing safety sensors and/or other components. There were a few cases where I had to replace larger mechanical equipment such as a blower wheel and blower motor swell.

Education

AEC / DEP or Skilled Trade Certificate in Computer Science

University of Toronto - Toronto, ON April 2021 to September 2021

College Degree in HVAC

George Brown - Casa Loma Campus - Toronto, ON September 2012 to April 2015

Skills

• HVAC Technician (6 years)

• Microsoft Office (8 years)

Certifications and Licenses

Gas Technician 2

May 2016 to Present

Gastite

October 2014 to Present

System 363 IPEX

September 2015 to Present

WHMIS

October 2011 to Present

Working at Heights

December 2019 to Present

4-Step Worker

Present

ODP

October 2020 to Present